At this point, you can probably tell
which one I prefer when in my own
personal coding. That being said, you
are going to run into all of them are
viable ways of handling asynchronous
code. Um, the most common ones that
you're going to see are async and awaits
and the then um the then chain that I
showed you. Um, in fact, they call
promises thenable objects. Um, but
because both of those are valid, I will
continue to show both throughout the
rest of this. Um, and we'll pick up from
there. But the next thing we need to
talk about is rejection. How do you
handle rejection? If you remember when I
gave you the broccoli in the promise and
when I explained what a promise was, I
gave you broccoli instead of ice cream
and you rejected it. We need to figure
out how to handle that with our
promises.